# Patrick J. King

2430 Westmount St. Apt.2 Halifax, NS B3L 3G7

902 292 4886

patkinghfx@gmail.com

I'm a highly adaptable and social person with a wide variety of experience in professions including management, service, craft brewing, gaming, tech, and film. I pride myself on being quick to learn and approaching situations with openmindedness and a positive nature.

# **RELEVANT WORK EXPERIENCE**

# Retail Manager, The Deckbox Halifax

Halifax, Nova Scotia -Nov 2020 - June 2022

#### Manager, Nearby Planet VR

Halifax, Nova Scotia — Sept 2016 - March 2017

#### **EDUCATION**

#### **NSCC eCampus**

IT Programming — Sept 2022 – Current Skills developed in this program include Web Development (HTML, CSS), Programming (Java), Database Management (mySQL) and Fundamentals of Networking and Security.

# **Center For Arts and Technology**

Digital Filmmaking — 2008 - 2010

This hands-on program encompassed film from start to finish - screenwriting, scheduling, shooting, editing and post-production. The skills required to be successful in this course included clear communication, project management, teamwork, technical skills, tight deadlines and creative problem solving.

# **SKILLS**

- Accredited screenwriter with excellent written and spoken communication.
- Highly proficient with both Mac and PC platforms as well as audio/video and hardware setups.

### **ACCOMPLISHMENTS**

- Using my knowledge of gaming I developed the popular 'Dungeons & Flagons' event at Good Robot Brewing in partnership with The Deckbox, which was so popular it was <u>featured by CBC</u>
- Worked with Director Luke Freeman on the screenplay for <u>Lord of Chaos</u> which was featured at the <u>Atlantic Film Festival 2015</u>
- Winner of The Coast's Best of Halifax Silver Award for Best Podcast

# **REFERENCES**

Johnny Heighton - Good Robot Brewing, Operations Manager Joshua Pyle-Carter - Owner & Operator, The Deckbox Thor Henrikson – Film Maker, Former Owner of Nearby Planet VR

Contact information available upon request